[{"question": " hey!", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 1, "asentId": 2}, {"question": " we're just here to say goodbye, we're off to ohio.", "answer": " oh, right! your adoption interview!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 3, "asentId": 4}, {"question": " yep, we're gonna meet the lady who could be carrying our baby.", "answer": " i can't believe it. when you guys come back, you're gonna have a baby! that is so weird!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 5, "asentId": 6}, {"question": " and so incorrect!", "answer": " she's only a couple of months pregnant. she liked our application but who knows if she's gonna like us.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 7, "asentId": 8}, {"question": " come on, she's gonna love you guys!", "answer": " uhm, thank you, but we're really trying not to get our hopes up.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 9, "asentId": 10}, {"question": " and a lot could still get in our way.", "answer": " yeah. i mean, this girl could decide against adoption or she could like another couple better..", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 11, "asentId": 12}, {"question": " what are you gonna name the baby?", "answer": " i can develop a condition in which i talk and talk and no one hears a word.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 13, "asentId": 14}, {"question": " but just think, ok? what if everything goes right? what if this woman does pick you guys?", "answer": " oh my god. she's gonna pick us!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 15, "asentId": 16}, {"question": " so we're standing firm on the 'not getting our hopes up'?", "answer": " you know, i know that things could still go wrong but if they don't? if this works out, we're gonna have a baby chandler, a baby!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 17, "asentId": 18}, {"question": " yes, but...", "answer": " oh my god, it's gonna work! we're gonna make it work! i'm gonna be a mummy and", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 19, "asentId": 20}, {"question": "  hey, who's phoebe with?", "answer": " i'm gonna say someone i'm gonna have sex with.   hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 23, "asentId": 24}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " so... who's your friend?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 25, "asentId": 26}, {"question": " oh, that's sarah. no, no. don't you get any ideas, ok? no, i'm not setting you up with any more of my friends!", "answer": " ow, why, why, why?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 27, "asentId": 28}, {"question": " because you'll date her once, sleep with her and then forget she exists!", "answer": " oh, name one friend of yours that i did that with.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 29, "asentId": 30}, {"question": " mandy.", "answer": " mandy, uh? uh... really hot blonde, big boobs?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 31, "asentId": 32}, {"question": " no.", "answer": " i know why i don't remember her, huh?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 33, "asentId": 34}, {"question": " do you think i'm someone else?", "answer": " ok, i may not have treated your friends well in the past, but i have grown up a lot, really. honest, rach?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 35, "asentId": 36}, {"question": " well, believe it or not, it's true. when joey and i were together, he was wonderful. he was thoughtful and mature. and for the one week that we went out, he didn't sleep with anybody else!", "answer": "  growth!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 37, "asentId": 38}, {"question": " fine, i'll give you her number.", "answer": " ok, thank you. and i promise you i will not forget this one.  mandy.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 39, "asentId": 40}, {"question": " sarah!", "answer": " saraaah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 41, "asentId": 42}, {"question": "  hey!", "answer": " hi!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 43, "asentId": 44}, {"question": " hey you guys, i need some fashion advice.", "answer": " oh!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 45, "asentId": 46}, {"question": "  how does this look?", "answer": " well, it's a little low... pick up a little...  a little bit more...  a little bit more...  there you go!  now throw it away!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 47, "asentId": 48}, {"question": " c'mon! this looks good!", "answer": " ross, please, trust me. i buy 30 fashion magazines a month. now, i don't know who's running for president or who that... nato guy is, but i do know that you have to get as far away as you can from that hat.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 49, "asentId": 50}, {"question": " damnit! i have this date tomorrow night and i have to look cool!", "answer": " well, you know, if you want fashion help, rachel and i are going shopping tomorrow. you're more than welcome to come with us, right?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 51, "asentId": 52}, {"question": " really? that would be great. i mean, i have to do something, she kinda teased me about how i dress.", "answer": " i can see why, nice shirt!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 53, "asentId": 54}, {"question": " you're wearing the same shirt.", "answer": " stupid gap on every corner!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 55, "asentId": 56}, {"question": " please, make yourself comfortable and i will back in a moment with erica.", "answer": " ok, thank you. uh, well this is it. are you ok?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 57, "asentId": 58}, {"question": " yeah. just weird, you know. it's like: &quot;hi, i'm chandler. may i have the human growing inside you?&quot;", "answer": " uh, we're gonna be great.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 59, "asentId": 60}, {"question": " you're gonna be great.", "answer": " well... obviously!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 61, "asentId": 62}, {"question": "  monica, chandler. i'd like you to meet erica.", "answer": " hi. it is so, so nice to meet you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 63, "asentId": 64}, {"question": "  hi...", "answer": " thank you so much for agreeing to see us.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 65, "asentId": 66}, {"question": " hi.", "answer": " i'll let you get acquainted.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 67, "asentId": 68}, {"question": " ok.", "answer": " so, it's monica and chandler. i only know you as file 0w33815-d.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 69, "asentId": 70}, {"question": " that's what our friends call us.", "answer": " gosh, you know, you're just such an amazing couple. it's... kind of intimidating.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 71, "asentId": 72}, {"question": " i don't know about that.", "answer": " you're kidding me? i mean, it's enough that you are a doctor. but on top of it, you're married to a reverend?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 73, "asentId": 74}, {"question": "  i don't think that's exactly...", "answer": "  let her finish, doctor.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 75, "asentId": 76}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " hey.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 77, "asentId": 78}, {"question": " oh, my friend sarah had a great time last night.", "answer": " well...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 79, "asentId": 80}, {"question": " yeah! so you're gonna call this one back?", "answer": " nope.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 81, "asentId": 82}, {"question": " what are you talking about? sarah's great!", "answer": " oh, really? you know what your great friend did? we're out to dinner, ok?  we're getting along, having a really nice time. i was thinking she was really cool. and then, out of nowhere...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 83, "asentId": 84}, {"question": " that&#8217;s it? that&#8217;s why you won&#8217;t go out with her again? so, she took some fries, big deal!", "answer": " hey, hey, look! it&#8217;s not about a few fries... it&#8217;s about what the fries represent.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 85, "asentId": 86}, {"question": " what?", "answer": " all food!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 87, "asentId": 88}, {"question": " i&#8217;m sorry, i can&#8217;t believe i set you up with such a monster!", "answer": " hey, hey, hey, hey. look. i take a girl out, she can order whatever she wants! the more, the better! all right? just don&#8217;t order a garden salad and then eat my food! that&#8217;s a good way to lose some fingers!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 89, "asentId": 90}, {"question": "  oh", "answer": " hi", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 91, "asentId": 92}, {"question": " thank god you&#8217;re here. listen to this!", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 93, "asentId": 94}, {"question": " joey and my friend were out last night and having dinner and she reaches over and takes a few of his fries...", "answer": " oh! oh, no!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 95, "asentId": 96}, {"question": " what? you know about the plate thing?", "answer": " oh, yeah. joey doesn&#8217;t share food. i mean, just last week we were having breakfast and he had a couple of grapes on his plate and ...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 97, "asentId": 98}, {"question": "  you wouldn&#8217;t let her have a grape?", "answer": " oh no! not me! emma!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 99, "asentId": 100}, {"question": "  joey doesn&#8217;t share food!", "answer": " well, i still think that it&#8217;s a stupid reason not to call someone again. you are calling her! and if you need to, just get an extra plate of fries for the table!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 101, "asentId": 102}, {"question": "  this place is awesome!", "answer": " you know, we should just go, i&#8217;m not gonna find anything here! this stuff is ridiculous!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 105, "asentId": 106}, {"question": " ah, this place is great!", "answer": " wow!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 107, "asentId": 108}, {"question": " rach, come on, i&#8217;m not gonna wear any of this!  nothing silver. . ok? nothing with hair!  and nothing with padlocks on it! .", "answer": " ross, look, i know that some of this stuff is out there, but i mean, come on, look at this, look at this sweater! . i mean, this is just beautiful!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 109, "asentId": 110}, {"question": "  wow, this is really soft . three hundred and fifty dollars?", "answer": " yeah, down from seven hundred, you are saving like two hundred bucks!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 111, "asentId": 112}, {"question": " both logic and math are taking a serious hit today. phoebe : hey, check this out! it&#8217;s totally you!", "answer": " wow!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 113, "asentId": 114}, {"question": " actually this looks like pretty good! yeah! boys will be boys?", "answer": " what? they will be!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 117, "asentId": 118}, {"question": " all right, that&#8217;s it, i&#8217;m getting out of here.", "answer": " no, no, no, no! ross, wait! come on! you know, there&#8217;s other stuff. here&#8217;s a nice shirt, look at these nice pants...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 119, "asentId": 120}, {"question": " uh, actually these might look pretty good on me.", "answer": " yes, they will! you know what you should do? just go take a walk, all right? i know your size and i&#8217;m... i&#8217;m gonna pick up some really good stuff for you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 121, "asentId": 122}, {"question": " really?", "answer": " yes! and i know what looks sexy on guys. please, just wear what i suggest, and she&#8217;s gonna go nuts for you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 123, "asentId": 124}, {"question": " so, you&#8217;re saying, uh, if i wear these pants i might be getting into hers?", "answer": "  why do men keep talking to me like this?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 125, "asentId": 126}, {"question": " so, the fact that i am a doctor, and my wife&#8217;s a reverend, that&#8217;s important to you?", "answer": " yeah, i read some great applications, but then i thought &#8220;who better then a minister to raise a child!&#8221;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 127, "asentId": 128}, {"question": " amen.", "answer": " plus i thought the baby would be in good hands with a doctor!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 129, "asentId": 130}, {"question": " uh, good hands.  healing hands.", "answer": " reverend, can i ask? does the bible say anything about adoption?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 131, "asentId": 132}, {"question": " it says &#8220;do it!&#8221;. and behold she did adopt onto them a baby. and it was good.", "answer": " wow.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 133, "asentId": 134}, {"question": " yeah, wow.", "answer": " i was wondering you both have such serious jobs.  would you have time to take care of a baby and your flock?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 135, "asentId": 136}, {"question": " oh, you know, my flock is good, i mean, yeah, my flock pretty much takes care of themselves at this point. good flock. flock, flock, flock.", "answer": "  being a doctor must take up a lot of time.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 137, "asentId": 138}, {"question": " so, how&#8217;s everything going in here?", "answer": " we&#8217;re great, i think i may have asked all my questions.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 141, "asentId": 142}, {"question": " do you have any question for erica?", "answer": " yeah, actually. so, you read a file that you liked and you gave the agency the serial number and they contacted us?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 143, "asentId": 144}, {"question": " yes, our system assures total anonimity. we&#8217;re very proud of it.", "answer": " you should be. you&#8217;re really on top of stuff..", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 145, "asentId": 146}, {"question": "  well, then if there&#8217;s nothing else, then the two of us should talk.", "answer": " actually, i don&#8217;t think we have to.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 147, "asentId": 148}, {"question": " we don&#8217;t?", "answer": " yeah, when i read about you two, i was pretty sure i wanted you, but i just thought we should meet face to face. . i've made my decision. i choose them.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 149, "asentId": 150}, {"question": " oh my god, this is great! this is so great! . did you hear that?", "answer": " yeah, i did.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 151, "asentId": 152}, {"question": " we got some really great stuff!", "answer": " yeah, yeah but i am not sure about some of the bra's i got.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 155, "asentId": 156}, {"question": " oh! really? do you wanna try some of them on for me?", "answer": " oh! okay. wait, are we in joey's imagination?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 157, "asentId": 158}, {"question": "  oh no! i took one of ross' bags by mistake, and one of mine is missing.", "answer": " oh, well, ross probably has it, you can get it from him later.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 159, "asentId": 160}, {"question": " i think were not wearing the same shirt anymore!!", "answer": "  yeah! yeah! rachel picked it out for me. she told me to trust her and you know what? i'm glad i did! i turned quite a few heads on my way over here.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 163, "asentId": 164}, {"question": "  dude, i really don't think you should be wearing that.", "answer": " oh, i see, somebody is afraid of a little competition with the ladies?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 165, "asentId": 166}, {"question": "  looks like someone is the ladies!!", "answer": " you're just jealous because you couldn't pull this off. yeah, now if you'll excuse me  i have a date.  see?  all eyes on me!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 167, "asentId": 168}, {"question": " we are not signing those papers.", "answer": " why not?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 169, "asentId": 170}, {"question": " it's wrong. they made a mistake. they think we're somebody else.", "answer": " god works in mysterious ways.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 171, "asentId": 172}, {"question": " you have gotta stop!", "answer": " but she liked us.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 173, "asentId": 174}, {"question": " she likes doctor chandler and reverend monica.", "answer": " well, if you think about it, i am kind of like a reverend. i mean, as a chef, i serve god, by feeing the hungry and poor.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 175, "asentId": 176}, {"question": " your veal chop is $34,95!", "answer": " c'mon chandler, i think we have been given an opportunity. i mean, the mistake has already been made. they are writing up the paper right now.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 177, "asentId": 178}, {"question": " but we are not the one she chose! how can you feel okay about this?", "answer": "  because... we may not be who she thinks we are but no-one will ever love that baby more than us.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 179, "asentId": 180}, {"question": " i know..", "answer": " i mean, who knows how long it's gonna take for someone else to give us a baby? what if, what if no one ever picks us?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 181, "asentId": 182}, {"question": " oh, honey..", "answer": "  please.. please, we are so close.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 183, "asentId": 184}, {"question": " monica, i want a baby too, but this woman is giving away her child. she deserves to know who it's going to.", "answer": "  okay, right.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 185, "asentId": 186}, {"question": " so, we'll tell the truth and who knows, maybe she'll like us for us.", "answer": "  maybe she will. uh! why couldn't i have been a reverend?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 187, "asentId": 188}, {"question": " you're jewish.", "answer": " technicality!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 189, "asentId": 190}, {"question": " oh, that looks great! good ordering!", "answer": " seafood platter for the gentleman and extra fries. enjoy!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 193, "asentId": 194}, {"question": " mmmh, those fries look delicious.", "answer": " oh, i didn't know you liked french fries. help yourself! what's mine is yours.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 195, "asentId": 196}, {"question": "  oh wow, are those stuffed clams?", "answer": " uuuh.. yes, they are my stuffed clams.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 197, "asentId": 198}, {"question": "  you are beautiful, you know that?", "answer": " oh, that is so sweet..", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 203, "asentId": 204}, {"question": "  now look what you did!!", "answer": " what? what is the matter with you?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 207, "asentId": 208}, {"question": " i don't like it when people take food off of my plate, okay?", "answer": " but you just said &quot;what's mine is yours&quot;?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 209, "asentId": 210}, {"question": " well, i didn't mean it!", "answer": " fine, i'm sorry, i didn't think it was that big a deal.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 211, "asentId": 212}, {"question": " wow, this place looks great.", "answer": " oh! you are gonna love it!  and i'm so glad, we're finally doing this.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 215, "asentId": 216}, {"question": " i really am sorry about, you know..before. i just want to make sure you know that i really do like you.", "answer": " sure  just not as much as clams.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 221, "asentId": 222}, {"question": " chocolate torte for the lady, cheesecake for the gentleman.", "answer": " uh, excuse me sir, there seems to be some sort of red crap on my cheesecake.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 225, "asentId": 226}, {"question": " yes, that's raspberry coule.", "answer": "  so stupid, ordering cheesecake, trying to be healthy.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 227, "asentId": 228}, {"question": " oh, all right, i'll just have what she's having instead.", "answer": " oh, i'm sorry sir, that was our last piece.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 231, "asentId": 232}, {"question": " oh, no! this is work. i should call in. can you excuse me?", "answer": " oh yeah, sure. no problem.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 235, "asentId": 236}, {"question": " what are you doing? i thought you don't share food.", "answer": " sure i do.  coule?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 237, "asentId": 238}, {"question": "  no. if i can't have your clams, you can't have my dessert. this is a two way street.", "answer": "  really?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 239, "asentId": 240}, {"question": " hi! adoption agency guy: hey.", "answer": " hey.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 253, "asentId": 254}, {"question": " so, these are the preliminary forms for an open adoption. there's a lot to go over, but i'll explain everything as we go through it.", "answer": "  i-is... is that a picture?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 255, "asentId": 256}, {"question": " look, doctor!  look, before we sign anything we really have to talk... we're not who you think we are.", "answer": " i don't understand.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 259, "asentId": 260}, {"question": " the agency must have made some mistake. my wife is not a reverend and i'm not a doctor.", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 261, "asentId": 262}, {"question": " that's impossible.", "answer": " i could perform an operation on you and prove it if you'd like.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 263, "asentId": 264}, {"question": " i'll go check your file. excuse me.", "answer": " so who are you?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 265, "asentId": 266}, {"question": " well, our names really are monica and chandler. we're from new york.", "answer": " yeah, but the important thing to know about us, is how much we would care for this little baby.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 267, "asentId": 268}, {"question": " so you lied to me before?", "answer": " well, we...  &quot;bore false witness&quot;... see i could be a reverend.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 269, "asentId": 270}, {"question": " i can't believe this.", "answer": " but we were hoping that since we told you the truth that you still might consider...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 271, "asentId": 272}, {"question": " giving you my baby? you think i'd give you my child after this?", "answer": " well, you don't have to decide right now, but if you could just look at our file...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 273, "asentId": 274}, {"question": " erica wait!", "answer": " i've nothing to say to you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 277, "asentId": 278}, {"question": " you have every reason to be upset. we did lie. but only because we've been waiting and trying to have a baby for so long. now we don't know how long it's gonna be before we can get another chance again.", "answer": " why don't you ask the reverend to pray on it?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 279, "asentId": 280}, {"question": " erica, please. just consider us. ask them to see our file. our last name's bing. my wife's a chef and i'm in advertising.", "answer": " oh yeah. i actually liked you guys. but it doesn't matter, because what you did was wrong.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 281, "asentId": 282}, {"question": " turns out this sweater is made for a woman.", "answer": "  so, why are you still wearing it?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 289, "asentId": 290}, {"question": " because it's soft... hey, so how was your date?", "answer": " ooh... not so good.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 291, "asentId": 292}, {"question": " well, looks like it's just the two of us tonight, huh old buddy?", "answer": " yeah, and you know what? we could do a lot worse.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 293, "asentId": 294}]